Now we have an application with the
capabilities and functionality well
definfined as intense to our spec. We'll
now add tests and documentation to my
application.
We want to add tests and documentation
to our project so that it's a robust
implementation of our spec. We'll ask
the agent to solidify our app by
generating docs and tests. You can see a
plan file is created that will go
through these various stages. Our spec
already has a list of capabilities. So
really, it's about making sure those are
runnable test scenarios that we can run
to validate that the generated code
adheres to the spec. Now the tests have
been generated, we can run them all, and
Tesla will cycle automatically through
the test failures, fixing them either by
altering the spec to be clearer, the
tests to ensure they're valid test
cases, or by rebuilding the code to
ensure it aderes to the specification.
We'll speed up this cycle for the sake
of this video, but it looks like we've
reached a stage where the majority of
our core tests are passing, and I can
continue iterating through the rest,
either with an agent or manually, to
achieve full coverage.
In our spec file, we see the
capabilities have all been retained, but
they now have matching test cases across
various test files. You can click
through to see the test files on the
file system to validate and ensure you
have the coverage you need. Since these
are Vitus files, you can run them
manually if you so choose. The tests are
grouped by file for each capability in
the same way you might do currently.
Additionally, we can see that a plan
file exists which captured all the
activity and actions that occurred
during our last session with Claude
code.
We now have a robust specentcentric
application that uses Tessle specs. Next
up, let's turn it into an express
server.